CARSON STURTEVANT

carson.sturtevant@gmail.com | (630) 247-2414 Westminster, CO

Well-rounded, enthusiastic software engineer with seven years of experience specializing in full-stack .NET development. Led multiple application feature projects from conception to production while guiding 2-3 team members. Top notch collaboration with multiple areas of the business including product management and devops to optimize the speed and guality of the solution.

WORK EXPERIENCE

Software Engineer - Reedgroup/Alight - Westminster, CO

2019-Present

- Full-stack C# .NET development with experience in SQL, MVC, WPF Services, JavaScript, Angular, Unit Testing,
 Web API, and Entity Framework.
- Highly flexible role, taking on a variety of projects across an entire suite of product offerings.
- Proficient in Agile and SAFe business organization. Quick adaptation to this model and provided guidance to peers on the most efficient agile practices emphasizing git flow and CI/CD.
- Noteworthy projects:
 - Multilingual support Developed to be used organization-wide for translating application content.
 - Oracle Integration Enhanced call center representatives' ability to provide quick and effective customer service.
 - Communications Hub Integrates with all applications across the organization to handle generation of all emails, letters and text messages. Customizable templating used internally by business partners.
 - Self-Service Portal Customer facing SaaS application used for leave absence management.

Software Developer - Calamos Investments - Naperville, IL

2016-2019

- Full-stack C# .NET developer with experience in SQL, Knockout, MVC, JavaScript, SSIS, SSRS, Unit Testing, Batch Processing, Web API, and Entity Framework.
- Expected to write clean, maintainable, and scalable code, provide support to users, be self-motivated, manage time efficiently, and work well alone or with co-workers.
- Interned at Calamos in 2015 and was offered a full-time position upon college graduation.
- Noteworthy projects:
 - Research database API .NET Core API built with code-first entity framework.
 - Distributed systems messaging queue used to integrate multiple platforms.
 - Portfolio data analytics UI design using a few JavaScript libraries, I creatively designed a way to display portfolio and risk management data, enhancing traders quick access to information.
 - o Integrated batch processing Developed workflows to process security, trade, and portfolio data.

EDUCATION & CERTIFICATIONS

Bachelor of Science (B.S.), Computer Science (May 2016)

• Illinois State University

Certified Cloud Practitioner (2021-2024)

Amazon Web Services (AWS)

REFERENCES

Available upon request.